rechargeaddict.in 2016-09-12

# Privacy Policy

****At www.rechargeaddict.in, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Recharge Addict collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a “User”) of the www.rechargeaddict.in website (“Site”). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by Recharge Addict.

 **Log Files: **  
Like many other Web sites, www.rechargeaddict.in makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

 **Cookies and Web Beacons:**  
www.rechargeaddict.in does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

 **DoubleClick DART Cookie: **  
• Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on www.rechargeaddict.in  
• Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to www.rechargeaddict.in and other sites on the internet.  
• Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html  
• Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include:: Google Adsense. These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on www.rechargeaddict.in send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and/or to personalize the advertising content that you see.www.rechargeaddict.in has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. www.rechargeaddict.in’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual  
browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with  
specific web browsers can be found at the browsers respective websites.

 **If you require any more information or have any questions about our  
privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at  
rechargeaddict@gmail.com**

Privacy Policy for  
www.rechargeoverload.inIf you require any more information or have any questions about our  
privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at  
latestfreerechargetrickz@gmail.com.At www.rechargeoverload.in, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme  
importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of  
personal information is received and collected by  
www.rechargeoverload.in and how it is used.Log Files  
Like many other Web sites, www.rechargeoverload.in makes use of log  
files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol (  
IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ),  
date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze  
trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and  
gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information  
are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.Cookies and Web Beacons  
www.rechargeoverload.in does use cookies to store information about  
visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages  
the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors  
browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their  
browser.DoubleClick DART Cookie  
.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on  
www.rechargeoverload.in.  
.:: Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users  
based on their visit to www.rechargeoverload.in and other sites on the  
Internet.  
.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the  
Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL –  
http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our  
site. Our advertising partners include ….  
Google Adsense  
Amazon

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the  
advertisements and links that appear on www.rechargeoverload.in send  
directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address  
when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or  
Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure  
the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the  
advertising content that you see.

www.rechargeoverload.in has no access to or control over these cookies  
that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party  
ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as  
for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices.  
www.rechargeoverload.in’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we  
cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual  
browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with  
specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

About us

we are only sharing this tweaks and tricks for information and  
educational purpose only .We are not promoting any hacks &  
fraudulent activity.  
0 comments:

Post a Comment

Home  
Click To Install  
Click To Install  
Subscribe Via Email

Subscribe to our newsletter to get the latest updates to your inbox. 😉

Your email address is safe with us!

Facebook  
Twitter  
Google+  
Linkedin  
Pinterest  
RSS

android cashback Earn money online free call free recharge freebie  
freecharge giveaway Mobikwik Network tricks Paytm shopping Telecom  
windows  
Popular Posts

Thumb  
Top 10 Highest Paying Android Apps 2015 for Free Mobile Recharge /  
Talktime  
All we know that mobile balance is how much important to us. In  
young generation mobile balance is more important than bank balance. We  
alw…  
Thumb  
Free Recharge Tricks – Get Unlimited Free Talktime On Paytm Mobile  
App January 2015  
Recently we have posted Earn Talktime & Mcent referral trick by  
which you can more free mobile recharge. All of us know that Paytm is  
…  
Thumb  
Install Snapdeal App and get Rs 50 Cash + Unlimited SD Cash Trick  
(Now Rs 50 Per Referral)  
Snapdeal App is giving Rs 50 snapdeal cash on sign up and Rs 50 for  
refer and earn. With the snapdeal cash reward money you can shop for  
an…  
Thumb  
Paytm Unlimited Recharge Tricks for Java / iPhone / Android / PC  
(Working Again)  
Paytm has removed the limitations of min Rs 50 transfer & to be 1  
month old account. So loot this offer again… 🙂 🙂 Today we are …  
Thumb  
RechargeKarle 110 Rs Talk Time for Rs 100  
RechargeKarle is an online prepaid recharge and booking solutions  
for online movie ticket booking, mobile and DTH recharge service, online  
…  
Thumb  
Install Greetz App via FreeB Recharge App and get Rs 105  
FreeB app is offering Rs 105 credits for installing a single app  
called Greetz. The offer is only for the first time installation of  
Greetz…  
Thumb  
Pay Rs 5 at Trideal and Get Rs 10 Cashback at Paytm  
Trideal is back with its paytm offer. Purchase a coupon worth Rs 5  
at trideal and get Rs 10 cashback at paytm. Also get upto Rs 9000  
cashba…

Alexa Certified Traffic Ranking for rechargeoverload.in

Source : <http://www.rechargeoverload.in/p/blog-page.html>  
Content Copyrighted to RechargeOverload.in

Privacy Policy  
Privacy Policy for www.rechargeoverload.inIf you require any more information or have any questions about our  
privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at  
latestfreerechargetrickz@gmail.com.At www.rechargeoverload.in, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme  
importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of  
personal information is received and collected by  
www.rechargeoverload.in and how it is used.Log Files  
Like many other Web sites, www.rechargeoverload.in makes use of log  
files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol (  
IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ),  
date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze  
trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and  
gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information  
are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.Cookies and Web Beacons  
www.rechargeoverload.in does use cookies to store information about  
visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages  
the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors  
browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their  
browser.DoubleClick DART Cookie  
.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on  
www.rechargeoverload.in.  
.:: Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users  
based on their visit to www.rechargeoverload.in and other sites on the  
Internet.  
.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the  
Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL –  
http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our  
site. Our advertising partners include ….  
Google Adsense  
Amazon

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the  
advertisements and links that appear on www.rechargeoverload.in send  
directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address  
when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or  
Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure  
the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the  
advertising content that you see.

www.rechargeoverload.in has no access to or control over these cookies  
that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party  
ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as  
for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices.  
www.rechargeoverload.in’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we  
cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual  
browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with  
specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

About us

we are only sharing this tweaks and tricks for information and  
educational purpose only .We are not promoting any hacks &  
fraudulent activity.  
0 comments:

Post a Comment

Home  
Click To Install  
Click To Install  
Subscribe Via Email

Subscribe to our newsletter to get the latest updates to your inbox. 😉

Your email address is safe with us!

Facebook  
Twitter  
Google+  
Linkedin  
Pinterest  
RSS

android cashback Earn money online free call free recharge freebie  
freecharge giveaway Mobikwik Network tricks Paytm shopping Telecom  
windows  
Popular Posts

Thumb  
Top 10 Highest Paying Android Apps 2015 for Free Mobile Recharge /  
Talktime  
All we know that mobile balance is how much important to us. In  
young generation mobile balance is more important than bank balance. We  
alw…  
Thumb  
Free Recharge Tricks – Get Unlimited Free Talktime On Paytm Mobile  
App January 2015  
Recently we have posted Earn Talktime & Mcent referral trick by  
which you can more free mobile recharge. All of us know that Paytm is  
…  
Thumb  
Install Snapdeal App and get Rs 50 Cash + Unlimited SD Cash Trick  
(Now Rs 50 Per Referral)  
Snapdeal App is giving Rs 50 snapdeal cash on sign up and Rs 50 for  
refer and earn. With the snapdeal cash reward money you can shop for  
an…  
Thumb  
Paytm Unlimited Recharge Tricks for Java / iPhone / Android / PC  
(Working Again)  
Paytm has removed the limitations of min Rs 50 transfer & to be 1  
month old account. So loot this offer again… 🙂 🙂 Today we are …  
Thumb  
RechargeKarle 110 Rs Talk Time for Rs 100  
RechargeKarle is an online prepaid recharge and booking solutions  
for online movie ticket booking, mobile and DTH recharge service, online  
…  
Thumb  
Install Greetz App via FreeB Recharge App and get Rs 105  
FreeB app is offering Rs 105 credits for installing a single app  
called Greetz. The offer is only for the first time installation of  
Greetz…  
Thumb  
Pay Rs 5 at Trideal and Get Rs 10 Cashback at Paytm  
Trideal is back with its paytm offer. Purchase a coupon worth Rs 5  
at trideal and get Rs 10 cashback at paytm. Also get upto Rs 9000  
cashba…

Alexa Certified Traffic Ranking for rechargeoverload.in

Source : <http://www.rechargeoverload.in/p/blog-page.html>  
Content Copyrighted to RechargeOverload.in

Privacy Policy  
Privacy Policy for www.rechargeoverload.inIf you require any more information or have any questions about our  
privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at  
latestfreerechargetrickz@gmail.com.At www.rechargeoverload.in, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme  
importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of  
personal information is received and collected by  
www.rechargeoverload.in and how it is used.Log Files  
Like many other Web sites, www.rechargeoverload.in makes use of log  
files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol (  
IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ),  
date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze  
trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and  
gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information  
are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.Cookies and Web Beacons  
www.rechargeoverload.in does use cookies to store information about  
visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages  
the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors  
browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their  
browser.DoubleClick DART Cookie  
.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on  
www.rechargeoverload.in.  
.:: Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users  
based on their visit to www.rechargeoverload.in and other sites on the  
Internet.  
.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the  
Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL –  
http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our  
site. Our advertising partners include ….  
Google Adsense  
Amazon

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the  
advertisements and links that appear on www.rechargeoverload.in send  
directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address  
when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or  
Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure  
the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the  
advertising content that you see.

www.rechargeoverload.in has no access to or control over these cookies  
that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party  
ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as  
for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices.  
www.rechargeoverload.in’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we  
cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual  
browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with  
specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

About us

we are only sharing this tweaks and tricks for information and  
educational purpose only .We are not promoting any hacks &  
fraudulent activity.  
0 comments:

Post a Comment

Home  
Click To Install  
Click To Install  
Subscribe Via Email

Subscribe to our newsletter to get the latest updates to your inbox. 😉

Your email address is safe with us!

Facebook  
Twitter  
Google+  
Linkedin  
Pinterest  
RSS

android cashback Earn money online free call free recharge freebie  
freecharge giveaway Mobikwik Network tricks Paytm shopping Telecom  
windows  
Popular Posts

Thumb  
Top 10 Highest Paying Android Apps 2015 for Free Mobile Recharge /  
Talktime  
All we know that mobile balance is how much important to us. In  
young generation mobile balance is more important than bank balance. We  
alw…  
Thumb  
Free Recharge Tricks – Get Unlimited Free Talktime On Paytm Mobile  
App January 2015  
Recently we have posted Earn Talktime & Mcent referral trick by  
which you can more free mobile recharge. All of us know that Paytm is  
…  
Thumb  
Install Snapdeal App and get Rs 50 Cash + Unlimited SD Cash Trick  
(Now Rs 50 Per Referral)  
Snapdeal App is giving Rs 50 snapdeal cash on sign up and Rs 50 for  
refer and earn. With the snapdeal cash reward money you can shop for  
an…  
Thumb  
Paytm Unlimited Recharge Tricks for Java / iPhone / Android / PC  
(Working Again)  
Paytm has removed the limitations of min Rs 50 transfer & to be 1  
month old account. So loot this offer again… 🙂 🙂 Today we are …  
Thumb  
RechargeKarle 110 Rs Talk Time for Rs 100  
RechargeKarle is an online prepaid recharge and booking solutions  
for online movie ticket booking, mobile and DTH recharge service, online  
…  
Thumb  
Install Greetz App via FreeB Recharge App and get Rs 105  
FreeB app is offering Rs 105 credits for installing a single app  
called Greetz. The offer is only for the first time installation of  
Greetz…  
Thumb  
Pay Rs 5 at Trideal and Get Rs 10 Cashback at Paytm  
Trideal is back with its paytm offer. Purchase a coupon worth Rs 5  
at trideal and get Rs 10 cashback at paytm. Also get upto Rs 9000  
cashba…

Alexa Certified Traffic Ranking for rechargeoverload.in

Source : <http://www.rechargeoverload.in/p/blog-page.html>  
Content Copyrighted to RechargeOverload.in
